When I was in fifth grade, I pointed
a gun at a man and killed him.
Let's go, bitch!
Fill it up or you get it, too!
Give me the money now or
I'm gonna kill her next!
I swear I'll do it!
You little give it back you brat!
Let go.
Let go of my gun!
I pulled the trigger three times.
Ever since that day,
if I saw a gun on TV or
even a picture of one,
it would trigger my PTSD and
send me into a panic attack.
Mets didn't help counseling didn't help
nothing helped me get rid of my phobia
I will help you to create something.
I will drop on my eyes.
I will put my love on your heart.
I will never know that I will never know.
But I'm not even happy with the world.
I'm not happy with the future.
I'm happy with the
eyes of my eyes.
I'm happy with the red
eyes of my eyes. I'm
happy with the sadness.
I'm happy with the sound of my eyes.
I thought if I got as far
away from home as I could.
To this high school in Tokyo.
I'd get better somehow.
But nothing changed.
Bang.
Looking back.
I don't have any regrets pulling
that trigger to protect my mom.
But the thing is.
I'm not strong enough to convince
myself it was the best choice either.
Despite being so screwed up, I
did make one friend in Tokyo.
He was the one who got me
into playing Gungale online.
Kyoji Shinkawa.
But I've been totally left behind.
That is so not true.
In the last qualifier, you made it all
the way to the semifinals, remember?
Whatever.
An AGI build only gets you so far in GGO.
A good gun helps, too.
I spent points on the wrong stat.
Don't get so down about that stuff.
Sign up for B .O .B.
and see what happens.
Nah, no point. I'd just die.
Uh-oh, it's late.
Sorry, I have to get going now.
Thanks for the tea. And thanks.
I mean, thank you for saving me.
You were pretty cool.
I wish I could always
be there to protect you.
Hey, uh, if you want, I can
walk you home every day.
I mean, if you want.
Oh, no, no, that's okay.
I'll be fine.
It's the only way I'll get stronger.
At the time, I was so focused on
taking care of me and getting better,
I didn't notice Kyoji's
true feelings for me.
In GGO,
I became Xenot, the Sniper,
and I made it my mission to
take on the strongest players.
Next!
Bullets are flying, and
he's got the guts to save.
Maybe I will, too, when I kill him.
I thought the stronger
Xenon got in the game,
the stronger I'd get in the real world.
I believed it with every fiber in me, so
I took on all comers with my Hecate II.
You're dead.
We're the governor's offices.
I was on my way over to sign up
for the prelims for the third
Bullet of Bullets tourney when I
met a player calling herself Kirito.
Turns out she was a he and insisted
on using a sword in a game of guns.
Boy, did he piss me off.
You're kidding!
No way!
You're a guy with that avatar?
Why, you—
Even though he pissed me off, I could
tell he was fighting his own demons.
Just like I was.
He won't even know what hit him.
Does he think he can dodge
my bullet at this range?
Does he even want to?
Don't, don't screw with me!
Fight me!
Come on, fight!
Or maybe you think I'm
not worth the effort!
You got it all wrong.
All I want is to compete in the final.
There's no reason to fight anymore.
Then go on and shoot yourself
and get it over with!
To you, it's just a game.
Just one stupid match.
That's all it is to
you, is that it? A game?
Well, just cause you feel
that way doesn't mean I do!
Xenon, give me a chance
to make it right with you.
Let me give you the fight I promised.
Okay, get set.
No way!
That's impossible!
You knew where I was
aiming but how how'd you
know I was going for
your leg I knew because
I Could see your eye
through the lens of your
scope that's how he
predicted my bullet's path
That's amazing that kind of
power is way beyond any vr game
If you're so strong you can do that,
why'd you look so afraid before?
You're wrong.
It's not strength.
All it is is a skill.
No, it's not.
Technique isn't enough to cut a
bullet from my Hecatee in half.
You and I both know that.
It takes strength and all I
want to know is how to get it.
It's what I...
It's what I'm here to figure out.
Listen,
could you shoot a player
in here if you knew
in the real world that
player would die from it?
And what if you had to kill that player?
Because if you didn't, you or
someone you love would die instead.
If you had that power, could
you still pull that trigger?
When death gun drew down on me, all
the hope i'd put into sinon's strength?
was shattered.
I type 54, Black Star.
It's the gun.
Why?
Why here?
Why does he have that gun?
Okay, then who's next?
I got a feeling that right
now in the real world,
Death Gun's partner's in your place.
He's watching the live stream, waiting
for when you get shot by that gun.
It's just a hunch.
No!
No, not that! Oh, God!
Until Death Gun shoots you, The guy in
your place isn't gonna do anything, okay?
That's the rule they
set up for themselves.
But if you log out now and
wake up with his partner there,
he'll kill you.
Tell me you got a plan.
We're going to take out Death Gun.
Please, Hecate.
I'm weak and I need your strength.
The strength to stand up
for myself and move on.
Concentrate.
Home in on his drive to kill.
Uh!
Get it out!
Gatia.
Damn it, he's tough.
If I can slow him down, in
one second's all I need!
Right now, Kirito's trying to get
that closure he was talking about.
He's confronting his demons from SAO by
taking on the person who represents them.
Death Gun.
And the reason he can
isn't cause he's strong.
It's cause he accepts what he did,
even though it still tears him up.
And he's still trying
to move on, despite it!
I've got to do something. Think!
Kirito!
Xenon's distracting him
with her bullet line.
She's got him in her sights,
using all her skill and spirit
to keep it trained on him.
It's like a phantom bullet!
One last attack.
I can't waste this chance!
Oh!
Fool.
It's not over yet.
You can't stop me.
He'll find you.
And he'll...
No, Zaza.
You're done.
And we'll find your partner, too.
He won't kill anyone anymore.
Laughing Coffin's dead.
It's over.
Yeah.
My name is Shino.
Shino Asura.
I guess now we should probably
get this tourney over with, huh?
Yeah, we should.
There.
I love you, Asuna.
I thought once I got to be the
strongest player in Gungale Online,
it'd somehow cancel out my
weakness in the real world.
I couldn't have been more wrong.
Run, Sinon!
I realized Sinon and Shino were the same.
They were me.
Come on, are you okay?
I know I won't get better overnight.
It's going to be a long time before I can
come to grips with the
memory of what I did.
Even so, little by
little, I will get better.
It's okay.
This world isn't that scary anymore.
It's pretty nice, actually?
Oh?
Next time, the Queen of the Lake.